声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman
校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
爸爸  你午饭时喝了多少酒
How many drinks did you have at lunch,dad?
你是在教训我么?
Are you lecturing me?
一个护士告诉我你的手在颤抖
One of the nurses told me that your hands were shaking.
女士们先生们,在我专业的观点看来
In my professional opinion,ladies and gentlemen
我被叫来的时候
by the time I was called in
病人已经无法挽救了
the damage was irreversible
我需要...
I need to...
修正一下我所说的
revise my statement.
在手术正常进行后我才进入手术室
I didn't come into the O.R. until well into the procedure.
我到这里的时候  这已经很清楚了
by the time I got there,it was clear
我父亲切断了病人的肝动脉
that my father severed the patient's hepatic artery
以我专业的观点看来
which,in my professional opinion
这直接导致了她的死亡
led to her death.
亲爱的Sawyer先生
"Dear Mr. Sawyer
你不知道我是谁但是我知道你做了什么
you don't know who I am,but I know what you've done.
你和我妈妈发生了关系，
You had sex with my mother
然后偷走了我爸爸全部的钱
and then you stole my dad's money all away.
总有一天  我会找到你 会给你这封信
One of these days,I'm going to find you and I'm going to give you this letter
这样你就会记住你对我所做的
so you'll remember what you done to me."
然后我看了信封
Then I looked at the envelope.
你写的这封信
You wrote this letter.
你的名字不是Sawyer   对吧?
Your name's not Sawyer,is it?
这是他的名字  他是一个骗子
It was his name. He was a confidence man.
为了钱  花言巧语骗了我妈
Romanced my mother to get to the money.
把我爸拥有的一切席卷一空  留下了一团糟
Wiped him out clean. Left a mess behind.
你只是个孩子
You were just a kid.
-快醒醒  -开门
-Wake up.  -Open this door!
-他来了  -开门
-He's here.  -Open this door!
快
Come on.
起床了
Got to get you up.
他会认为你仍然和你的爷爷奶奶在一起的
He'll think you're still with your grandparents,okay?
躲到床下去
Get under the bed.
快点  好么
Let's go. Okay.
听妈妈的  这真的很重要
Listen to mommy. This is really important.
躲到床下  别出声  别出来
Get under the bed. Don't make a sound. Don't come out.
不管发生了什么  别出来  好么
No matter what happens,don't come out,okay?
好的
Okay.
哦 上帝
Oh,god.
-我爱你  -我也爱你  妈妈
-I love you.  -I love you,too,mommy.
快  躲进去
Let's go. Down you go.
很好  一定别出声
All right,be real quiet.
Laura 开门
Laura,open this door!
住手
Stop it!
快住手
滚开
Go away!
你究竟是怎么了?
What the hell is wrong with you?
我要叫警察了  滚开
I'm calling the police! Get out of here!
你干什么? 你拿枪究竟想干什么? 出去...
What are you doing? What the hell are you doing with a gun? Get out --
它会回来的
It'll come back around.
油布被野猪弄走了?
Boar took your tarp?
当时很黑  但是  是的 我很肯定是一只野猪
It was dark,but,yeah,pretty sure it was a boar.
我认为这只野猪已经离开这儿了
I thought the boar had vacated this area.
强人  我认为有一些坏消息
genius,I think we got some bad info.
它在你帐篷里干什么?
What was he doing inside your tent?
它盯着我
It was staring at me.
然后它向我冲了过来  我打了它 然后它跑进了丛林
Then it came at me,so I hit it,and it ran off into the jungle.
带着你的油布
With your tarp.
或许他想去露营
Perhaps he wanted to go camping.
你很开心么?
You enjoying yourself?
是的
Yes.
笑出声来吧  穆罕默德
laugh it up,Muhammed.
但是我回来后发现我的东西没了
But I come back and find my stuff's gone
我跟着你
I'm coming after you.
Sayid?
你听到了什么?
What did you hear?
在你偶然遇到那个法国女人之后
After you ran into the French woman
你说你在丛林里听到了些什么
you said you heard something in the jungle.
我受伤了，精疲力竭  估计我脑子一下子糊涂了
I was injured and I was exhausted. My mind was playing tricks.
你听到什么了?
What did you hear?
我想我听到了有人在说悄悄话
I thought I heard whispering.
说了什么?
What was it saying?
怎么了?
你听到什么了?
Did you hear something?
算了  我什么都没听见
Forget it. I didn't hear anything.
你怕什么啊?
What are you so afraid of?
在发抖的是你，亲爱的
You're the one trembling,sweetness.
好了 虽然这真的很愚蠢
Okay,this is really awkward.
但是如果我现在不开口的话
But if I don't say something now
事情就会变得更让人为难了
things are liable to get downright embarrassing.
Hibbs
你好 Sawyer
Hello,Sawyer.
夫人 我想道歉
Ma'am,I must apologize.
我以为我的好朋友Sawyer 会一个人在这儿
I figured my good friend Sawyer here would be alone.
我只要一下就好
I just need a few minutes.
听着  亲爱的...
Listen,baby...
-亲爱的  他是谁? -听着
-Baby,who is this?-Listen.
你去下面的酒吧喝点什么吧
You go down to the bar. You get a drink.
不  我不想把你留在这儿
No,I don't want to leave you here.
我一摆脱他后马上...
As soon as I get rid of him,
去找你  然后向你解释一切
then I'll come get you and I'll explain everything.
-但是...  -听着
-But...  -Listen.
相信我吧  我会找到你的
Just trust me on this. I will find you.
我保证  相信我
I promise. Promise.
你说说  Sawbucks...
I got to hand it to you,Sawbucks...
你是怎么骗到这么漂亮的女人的
how you find women that beautiful to work your grift.
如果我现在没错的话
Now,if I'm not mistaken
我记得很清楚 我说过我再次见到你我会杀了你
I'm fairly certain I said I'd kill you if I ever saw you again.
所以我来了
That's why I'm here.
处理好一切
To make things right.
况且  我们都知道你不是杀人的人
Besides,we both know you ain't the killing type.
这个
Here.
我想我们在Tampa那件事上扯平了
Figure that makes us even for the Tampa job.
我们怎么可能在Tampa那件事上扯平呢
What could possibly make us even for the Tampa job?
那么关于那个毁了你一生的男人 他的下落呢?
How about the known whereabouts of the man who ruined your life?
我想来点喝的  你呢?
I'm gonna make myself a drink. You want one?
你记得那老家伙Parks么?
You remember old man Parks,right?
在亚特兰大那个马车上 帮我们支起顶棚的那个家伙?
Ran capper for us on that gig in Atlanta?
是的  他怎样了?
Yeah,what about him?
他在悉尼的一家出线业务室拍电报
He's been working the wire at an off-track parlor down in Sydney.
上周
So last week,
他的一位常客鲁莽了些
one of his regulars gets a little too sauced,
把他的骗子生涯 给揭了个底儿朝天
starts running his mouth off about his glory days as a grifter.
那家伙  Frank Duckett
That guy. Frank Duckett.
真是一个不幸的人  沉迷于赌博和酒精
Real hard-luck case --gambling addict,alcoholic.
开一辆小卡车
Runs a shrimp truck.
想起来  Duckett这家伙还真是会骗
Back in the day,this guy Duckett was quite the hustler.
他善于使感情骗术
He ran the romance angle.
把别人老婆骗上钩  再拿走她老公所有的钱
Hook the wife,take the husband for all the money.
我听说他还真在行
Was pretty good at it,too,from what I hear.
直到其中一个人被他骗得伤心欲绝
Until sadly one of his marks in despair
带着枪  杀了他的妻子 然后饮弹自尽
took a gun,shot up his wife,and blew his own head off.
他们的小儿子目睹了所有的一切
All in front of their little boy.
我雇Tony偷走了他的夹克
I paid Tony to pull his jacket.
看来Frank Duckett曾经叫Frank Sawyer
Turns out Frank Duckett used to be named Frank Sawyer,
一个我认为很适合你的名字
a name I believe you appropriated for yourself.
这就是他?
This is him?
是的
That's him.
多谢债主
Thanks for the loaner.
没关系
Always a pleasure.
那么有人好奇它们从哪儿来么?
So is anyone curious where they came from?
他们都知道有位长官在飞机上
The others knew there was a marshal on the plane.
我猜他们认为他在单独做事
I guess they just assumed he was traveling alone,
保护他们不受恐怖分子侵害
protecting them from terrorists.
对我来说是个不错的理论
Sounds like a good theory to me.
你拿回了所有的枪么?
Did you get all the guns back?
除了一枝
All except one.
我让你猜三下怎么样?
How about I give you three guesses?
Sawyer
我能拿回的
I can get it back.
真的
Really.
你怎么拿?
How are you gonna do that?
说他的语言
Speak his language.
你已经这样做过了  Kate
You've done this before,Kate
如果我没记错
and if I remember it right
你了解他
you made out with him
你说你能拿到的东西他连有都没有
and he never even had what you said you could get.
我唯一了解的是他不吃硬的
Well,I only made out with him because torturing him didn't work.
枪让他留着吧  不值得这么做
Let him keep the gun. It's not worth it.
你担心如果我说了他会向我开枪?
You worried he's gonna shoot me if I ask?
我只是不想你欠他什么
I just don't want you to owe him anything.
感觉怎么样?
How you feeling?
感觉快生了
Very pregnant.
我昨晚做了几个梦
I had some dreams last night.
其实  很像是回忆
Actually,more like memories.
你也在里面
You were in them.
不好意思
Sorry.
我想你是不是想去走走
Thought I'd see if you wanted to go for a walk.
不了
Sorry.
我要...
I have to...
做点事
do something.
一会儿见  好么?
See you later,okay?
它会回来的
It'll come back around.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
全是一只野猪干的?
A boar did all this?
昨晚  它毁了我的帐篷
Last night,he wrecked my tent.
今天早上 当我去拿回我的帐篷的时候
This morning,when I went to get my tent back,
它从后面攻击了我
it attacks me from behind,
然后像个懦夫一样跑进了丛林
runs off into the jungle like a coward.
野猪不会无缘无故地攻击你
A  boar wouldn't just attack you for no reason.
谢了  野猪专家
Thank you,boar expert.
这只就是这样的
This one did.
烦死我了
It's harassing me.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
摆平它
Getting even.
你听听你自己在说些什么  只是一只野猪而已
Would you listen to yourself? It's a boar.
告诉Locke  他会宰了它的
Just go tell Locke,and he'll kill it.
不 我要亲自宰了它
Nope. This is my fight.
你知道怎么狩猎野猪么
Do you know anything about hunting boar?
你会迷路甚至更糟
You are gonna get yourself lost or worse.
你从什么时候开始关心我了?
Since when do you care?
我没有
I don't.
很好  那么对不起了
Good. Then if you'll excuse me,
我准备去报仇
I've got some revenge to tend to.
你肯定是Hibbs的同伴
You must be Hibbs's mate.
我回美国后和Hibbs一起干了一些事
I did a few jobs with Hibbs back in the States.
够了吧  伙计
Nice enough fella.
-他是个混蛋  -对  他的确是
-He's a son of a bitch.  -Right. Indeed he is.
有一些免责声明
A few disclaimers.
澳大利亚不允许居民携带手枪
Australia doesn't allow its citizens to carry handguns.
你挑挑看这个的毛病...
You get nicked with this...
我不想让你颜面尽失
I'm not gonna rat you out.
还有你知道的 我已经做了一段时间了
Secondly,you know,I've been doing this for a while,
一个人买了把带空心弹夹的紧凑型USP357SIG
and a man who buys a compact .357 with hollow-point loads --
他不准备去吓人或是偷东西
he's not looking to scare or steal.
他是去杀人
He's looking to kill.
直到了杀人的时候
But  when it comes down to it,
他却发现自己没有勇气下手
if he finds he doesn't have what it takes to do the job...
你还要改进你的买卖程度
Your sales pitch needs some work.
我要说的是...
What I'm saying is...
你看着一个人并且拿枪指着他
you look a man in the eye and you point a gun at him,
你知道你真正是谁了  伙计
you find who you really are,mate.
如果你发现你不是一个杀手的话 是没有退款的
And should you find you're not a killer,there's no refund.
这不是问题
It won't be a problem.
Hurley
很感谢你的帮忙
I appreciate the help
但是你不需要这么做...
but you don't have to...
我杀了Ethan
I killed Ethan.
我能埋了他
I can bury him.
是的  直到他复活
Yeah,until he rises from the dead.
伙计  我知道这会怎样
Dude,I know how this works.
这会毁了我和你
This is gonna end with you and me
跑过丛林  叫喊  哭喊
running through the jungle,screaming and crying.
他会先抓到我  因为我很重而且
He catches me first because I'm heavy and
我抽筋了
I get cramps.
你还好么?
Are you all right?
你好 Sayid
Yo. Sayid.
我能问你个问题么?
Can I ask you a question?
当然
Of course.
你得过海湾战争综合症么?
Did you ever get that Gulf War syndrome?
那是另一个方面
That was the other side.
对
right.
其中一部分像是炮弹休克?
Then what's the one where they're all,like,shell-shocked?
外伤后的压力紊乱
Post-traumatic stress disorder.
对  就是这个  你得过么?
Yeah,that's it. Did you ever have that?
你为什么这么问?
Why do you ask?
因为我担心Charlie
Because I'm worried about Charlie.
Charlie怎么了?
What's wrong with Charlie?
我是说  他杀了个人
I mean,he killed a guy.
他向他胸口开了四枪
He shot him in the chest four times
或许你能找他谈谈?
Maybe you should talk to him?
是个脚印
It's a footprint.
基于这个重量和步幅的宽度 我说...
Based on the weight and the distance between strides,I'd say...
你一直在跟着Boone约摸有一个小时了
you've been following Boone for about an hour.
看...
Look...
我猜可能是Charlie
Could be Charlie,I suppose.
我对你这么关心我的事感到很好笑
I'm tickled you have taken such an interest in my affairs.
真的
I really am.
所以不要以个人的观点来处事 当我说...
So don't take it personal when I tell you to go...
-我要全权委托  -什么?
-I want carte blanche.  -What?
没我的帮忙你根本找不到这只野猪
You can't track this boar without my help.
过去的几个小时...
Over the last few hours...
你只是在设法跟踪人和鸟
you have managed to follow the tracks of humans,birds,
岩石的滑动 你自己... 基本上跟野猪都没什么关系
a rock slide,yourself --basically everything except boar.
你不知道你在做什么
You have no idea what you're doing.
全权委托...
Carte blanche...
意味着空白支票
It means "blank check."
我知道它的意思
I know what it means.
每次我从你隐蔽的地方找到...药 肥皂 无论什么...
Anytime I want something from your stash...medicine,soap,whatever
我都得到了 从没问过什么
I get it,no questions asked.
带走或留着
Take it or leave it.
好吧
All right
做个交易
You got a deal.
-你在什么地方拿到的?  -飞机上
-Where'd you get that?  -The plane.
Jack正在找这瓶酒
Jack was looking for the liquor cart.
我找到了个代替的 不是很好么  嗯?
It's a good thing I found it instead then?
那还有么?
Got any more of those?
我每样东西都还有很多
I got a lot more of everything,
但你还不能全权委托
but you ain't got carte blanche yet.
那就是表示不行了?
Is that a no?
好了 Sassafras
All right,Sassafras.
但是如若你想喝的话  你得玩个游戏
But if you want a drink,you gotta play.
玩什么?
Play what?
"我从来不..."的一种游戏(一个喝酒游戏)
I never.
什么?
What?
我从来不
I never.
我能知道那是什么意思吗
Am I supposed to know what that means?
就叫它增进相互了解的方法吧
Call it a way to get to know each other better.
比如
For example,
我知道你从没上过大学
I know you've never been to college.
你怎么知道的?
And how do you know that?
如果你去了 你肯定听过"我从来没有"
If you had,you'd have heard of "I never."
这很简单
It's simple.
你说"我从来没有" 然后你说完整个句子
You say "I never," and then you finish the sentence.
如果是你做过的话  你就喝一口酒
If it's something you did,you drink.
如果你没做过的话
If it's something you never did
你就不能喝
you don't drink.
那真是没意思
That makes absolutely no sense.
举个例子
Learn by example.
我从没吻过男人
I never kissed a man.
现在你可以喝了
Now you drink
因为你吻过男人
cause you've kissed a man.
该你了
我从没暗示过我上过大学 事实也是我从没上过
I never implied that I've been to college when I never have.
我没去过迪士尼乐园
I never been to Disneyland.
真可怜
that's just sad
我从没穿戴过粉色的衣物
I never wore pink.
我知道
I knew it.
-80年代的  -恩 是的
-The '80s.  -Mm-hmm.
我从没选过民主党人
I never voted democrat.
我从没选过
I never voted.
我从没谈过恋爱
你从没谈过恋爱?
You've never been in love?
我没喝  不是么?
I ain't drinking,am I?
我从未有过一夜情
I've never had a one-night stand.
干了  水手
Bottom's up,sailor.
我得为每句话都喝么?
I gotta drink for each one?
该你了
Your turn.
我从没结过婚
I never been married.
那并没持续多久
It didn't last very long.
我从没把问题都发泄到野猪头上去
I've never blamed a boar for all my problems.
我从没担心过拥有全权委托
I never cared about having carte blanche
因为我只是想消磨一点时间
cause I just wanted to spend some time
和在这个岛上唯一的另一个人一起
with the only other person on this island
那并不合适
that just don't belong.
我从没随身携带一封信20年之久
I never carried a letter around for 20 years
因为我的包放不下
because I couldn't get over my baggage.
我从没杀过人
I never killed a man.
这...
Well...
看来我们还是有些共同点的
it looks like we got something in common after all.
它会回来的
It'll come back around.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
你在发抖
You're shaking.
我很好
I'm fine.
我只是有点...
I was just having a...
不敢相信
I can't believe this.
到处都是蹄印
There are hoof marks everywhere.
它吃了我们所有的东西?
It ate all our stuff?
不  它只吃了你的东西
Nope. It ate your stuff.
我的还在
Mine's fine.
那野猪一定会受到惩罚  我向天发誓...
that hogis gonna suffer. I swear to god...
早上好
Morning.
你们的野营地怎么了?
What happened to your campsite?
你从那么远跑来干什么  John?
So,what are you doing all the way out here,John?
做坠机的营救工作
Looking for salvage from the crash.
找到有用的么?
Find anything useful?
特殊的金属片...两袋咖啡
The occasional scrap of metal... two bags of coffee.
我沿着你的路回走了一英里找到的  我该跟你打个招呼吧
I picked up your path about a mile back. I thought I'd say howdy.
狗娘的
son of a...
他在我衬衫上撒尿
He peed on my shirt.
他把我衬衫从袋子里拉出来后 还在上面撒尿
He took my shirt out of the bag and peed on it.
你说这不是针对个人的
And you say this ain't personal.
他认为我们跟踪的野猪和他有深仇大恨
He thinks the boar we're after has a vendetta against him.
它攻击我三次了
That's three times it's attacked me.
可能它闻到了你的味道 不喜欢你的古龙水
Maybe it's got your scent. Doesn't like your cologne.
我不喷古龙水
I don't wear cologne.
不对 你喷的
Yes,you do.
好吧  呃...
Yeah,well...
问题是他是冲着我来的
the thing's got it in for me!
只是只野猪  Sawyer
It's a boar,Sawyer.
我妹妹Jeannie在我还小的时候就死了
My sister Jeannie died when I was a boy.
她摔下了猴栏扭断了脖子
She fell off the monkey bars and broke her neck.
我的母亲  呃  我的养母
And my mother...well,my foster mother...
她很自责  毫无疑问
she blamed herself,of course
认为她自己没有看紧
Thought she wasn't watching close enough.
所以她不吃不睡
So she stopped eating,stopped sleeping.
邻居们开始议论
The neighbors started talking
我猜他们怕她会对自己做些什么
afraid she might do something to herself,I guess.
很不错
that's good.
无论如何 大约在Jeannie的葬礼6个月后
Anyway,about six months after Jeannie's funeral,
这只金毛猎犬挡住了我们的车道
this golden retriever comes padding up our driveway,
直冲着我们家来 坐在地上
walks right into our house,sits down on the floor,
并且直盯盯地看着睡椅上的我的母亲
and looks right at my mother there on the couch.
我的母亲也看着它
And my mother looks back at the dog.
大约1分钟时间
After about a minute of this...
他们互相看着对方  就像这样
them both staring at each other like that...
我母亲泪流满面
my mother burst into tears.
很漂亮的狗  没有标牌 没有项圈 健康可爱
Beautiful dog --no tags,no collar. Healthy and sweet.
这只狗睡在Jeannie的房间 Jeannie的床上
The dog slept in Jeannie's old room on Jeannie's old bed
并一直和我们呆在一起 直到我母亲5年后去世
and stayed with us until my mother passed five years later,
然后消失了  回到...
then disappeared back to...
无论哪里  反正回到她原来呆着的地方
wherever it was she came from in the first place.
那么... 你说这只狗是你妹妹?
So... you're saying the dog was your sister?
虽然那很愚蠢
that would be silly.
但我母亲认为是
But my mother thought it was.
认为Jeannie回来告诉她
Thought that Jeannie had come back to tell her
这事故不是她的错
the accident wasn't her fault
让她摆脱自责
let her off the hook.
你的外卖
You're good to go.
温合口味的沙司虾或辣沙司虾
Only two choices --shrimp in mild sauce,shrimp in hot sauce.
我要辣的
I'll go with the hot.
好  辣的
Hot it is.
你是美国的 是吗
a fellow American,huh?
是的
Good for you.
你错过了午餐高峰
You missed the lunch rush.
你从哪儿来?
Whereabouts you from?
田纳西州
Tennessee.
我喜欢南部
I love the south.
想念南部的女人
Miss those southern women.
来澳大利亚很久了?
Been in Australia long?
没多久
Not really.
好消息
For what it's worth,
我们卡车里有特价
we have a special at the truck here...
美国人一律半价
half-price for all Americans.
顺便说一下  我叫Frank
Name's Frank,by the way.
James
很高兴见到你  James
Good to meet you,James.
一份辣沙司虾...
One  shrimp in hot sauce...
又一次了
Again.
你很肯定么  伙计?
Are you sure about that,mate?
又一次了
Again.
你告诉他  小子
You tell him,cowboy.
这些混蛋以为美国人控制不了自己的酒量
These bastards think Americans can't hold their liquor.
看 我
Look,I
我讨厌罢手 但好像我把我钱包放错地方了
I hate to hold my hand out,but I seem to have misplaced my wallet.
把他弄好
Set him up.
和你喝一杯
I drink to you.
小子  你叫什么?
What's your name,cowboy?
Sawyer
向Sawyer干杯
To Sawyer.
愿他找到在杯子底的他想找的东西
May he find whatever he's looking for at the bottom of a glass.
那么  Sawyer...
So,Sawyer...
你为什么来悉尼的?
what brings you to Sydney?
工作需要
Business.
你知道为什么大家把澳大利亚叫做"下下之地"么?
You know why they call australia "down under," don't you?
因为它跟地狱差不多近
Because it's as close as you can get to hell
但不会烧着
without being burned.
过来吧  伙计
How about you leave the bottle,slim?
你在美国是做什么的?
So,what's your handle back in the states?
我曾经是一个...
I was a...
外科主刀医生
chief of surgery.
曾经?
Was?
是的，曾经
Yeah,I was.
这么说我们身处地狱?
So we're in hell?
别让这里的环境迷惑了你  伙计
Don't let the air conditioning fool you,son.
你也在这儿
You are here,too.
并且你在苦难中
And you are suffering.
但是别为此折磨你自己
But don't beat yourself up about it.
这是命运
It's fate.
一些人命该受难
Some people are just supposed to suffer.
这就是为什么红袜队从没赢过可恶的赛季
That's why the Red Sox will never win the damn series.
我有一个儿子  他和你差不多大
I have a son --he's about your age.
他和我不一样
He's not like me.
他做他想做的事
He does what's in his heart.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
可能很伟大
Maybe a great one.
现在..
And right now...
他认为我恨他
he thinks that I hate him.
他认为我感觉他背叛了我
He thinks I feel betrayed by him.
但是我真正感到的是...
But what I really feel...
感谢和自豪
is gratitude and pride
为了他对我所做的
because of what he did to me.
他为我所做的
What he did for me.
这需要比我更多的勇气
It took more courage than I have.
那有一个投币电话
There's a pay phone over here.
我可以用它来给我儿子打电话
I could pick it up,and I could call my son.
我能告诉他全部这些话
I could tell him about all of this.
我能告诉他我爱他
I could tell him that I love him.
一个简单的电话就能弥补一切
One simple phone call,and I could fix everything.
那你为什么不打呢?
Then why don't you?
因为我很软弱
Because I am weak.
这个
This
你的工作...
this business that you have...
能减轻你的痛苦么?
will it ease your suffering?
是的
Yeah.
那么你在这儿干什么?
Then what are you doing here?
这没这么简单
It ain't that simple.
当然很简单
Of course it is.
当然很简单  除非你想和我的下场一样
Unless you want to end up like me,of course it is.
你很有天份
You're developing quite a talent.
是的
Yeah.
我知道了
I get it.
你是来看我的
You're here to check up on me.
你杀了个人
You killed a man.
那个人杀了我们其中一个
A man who killed one of us.
他绑架了Claire
Who kidnapped Claire.
他把我绑起来让我等死  他该死
Who strung me up and left me for dead. He deserved to die.
我立刻就可以再做一次
I'd do it again in a minute.
原谅我  我发泄了我的不快
Pardon me if I'm fresh out of bad feeling.
当我在伊拉克Tikrit的军队时
When I was in the army in Tikrit in Iraq,
住在我隔壁的是一个警察
the man who lived next door was a policeman.
有天他的车被安上了炸弹
One day his car was rigged with a bomb.
炸死了他的妻子和三个小孩
It killed his wife and three young children instead.
他们抓住了罪魁祸首
They caught the man who did it.
我志愿参加行刑队
I volunteered to be on the firing squad,
然后我毫不留情得履行了我的职责
and I did my duty without a single ounce of remorse.
然后不知为什么
Then for no reason
我晚上醒来了
I found myself waking up at night
脑子里回忆着我所做的
replaying what I did in my head.
你才是那个我要找的人
Looks like you're the one who needs checking up on.
我所说的是关于Ethan的事
All I'm saying is that what happened with Ethan
这些事将会伴随你一生
will be with you for the rest of your life.
有什么建议么?
Any suggestions?
你并不孤单
You're not alone.
别假装孤独
Don't pretend to be.
让我欣慰的是有天
I take comfort knowing someday
这里会变成一个很好的购物区
this is all gonna be a real nice shopping complex
甚至可能是一个汽车购物区
Maybe even an automall.
你去哪儿?
Where you going?
知道那是什么么?
Know what that is?
一团泥巴洞
A whole in the mud.
一个泥坑
It's a wallow.
什么是泥坑?
What the hell's a wallow?
野猪的坑
Boar's wallow.
是它睡觉的巢穴
It's his den where he sleeps.
这些树上是他牙齿戳后的痕迹
And these tree rubbings from his tusks.
你是说它在附近?
You mean he's around here?
可能吧
Maybe.
等等  Sawyer
Wait,Sawyer.
抓住你了
Gotcha!
我以为它会比这大
I thought it'd be bigger.
真有趣 现在我们知道它爸爸就在这附近
Funny. Now we know daddy's got to be around here.
在这儿 小猪 小猪 小猪
Here,piggy,piggy,piggy!
Sawyer  放下它 这不是闹着玩儿的
Sawyer,put it down! That's not funny!
在这儿 小猪 小猪 小猪
Here,piggy,piggy,piggy!
你怎么了 Sawyer?
Hey,what is the matter with you,Sawyer?
你会伤了它的
You're gonna hurt it!
我们在这儿
We're right over here!
-在这儿 小猪
-Here,piggy.
-你有病  -我没伤害它
-You're sick.  -I didn't hurt it.
你自己回去吧
Find your own way home.
没问题
No problem!
Sawyer
我有一封你的信
I got a letter for you.
亲爱的Sawyer先生
"Dear Mr. Sawyer..."
谁?
Who?
你曾经用过Sawyer这个名字
You used to go by the name of Sawyer.
你究竟在说什么?
What the hell are you talking about?
你不必这样做
You didn't have to.
告诉Hibbs我会给钱的
Tell Hibbs I would have paid.
你怎么知道Hibbs?
How do you know Hibbs?
你不...
You don't...
你不知道你在做什么  是不是?
you don't know what you're doing,do you?
你问Hibbs借过钱了?
You borrowed money from Hibbs?
我会还的
I was gonna pay.
它会回来的
It'll come back around.
Kate
这只是一只野猪
It's just a boar.
我们回营地吧
Let's get back to camp.
现在可以去走走了吗?
Want to take that walk now?
好的
Sure.
竖起它们
Stick 'em up.
想搞笑么?
Trying to be funny?
是的
Yeah.
给你扔几个馅饼怎么样?
I was fresh out of pies to throw at you.
给你 长官
Here you go,sheriff.
我两天前就问你要了
I asked you for this two days ago.
我告诉你再忍一会儿
And I told you to stick it.
但是我和你女朋友达成了个协议
But I made a deal with your girlfriend.
她给了你什么?
What did she give you?
Kate  她给了你什么?
Kate. What did she give you?
没有  她不准备放弃
Nothing she wasn't willing to part with.
这就是为什么红袜队从没赢过赛季
That's why the Red Sox will never win the series.
你刚说了什么?
What'd you just say?
我说这就是为什么红袜队不可能赢整个赛季
I said that's why the Red Sox will never win the series.
这究竟是什么意思?
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
这是我爸老说的
It's just something my father used to say
所以他可以用一生来知道人们恨他
so he could go through life knowing that people hated him.
并且他只是用命运来搪塞 推卸责任
Instead of taking responsibility for it,he just put it on fate.
说是这是注定的
Said he was made that way.
你爸爸...
Your daddy...
也是一个医生?
he a doctor,too?
是的
Was.
他死了
He's dead.
你为什么想了解我的爸爸?
Why do you want to know about my father?
没什么
No reason.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====